Thank you for the support of the City of Miami.
Thank you for our interim city manager, our mayor, the city council members,
city employees, the businesses, the churches, the families, and the individuals
that make our city the community that it is.
We pray for this council meeting tonight.
We ask you to give the council members wisdom and guidance as they celebrate
on the items before them, as deliberate on the items before them.
May every decision be righteous in your sight for our benefit and for your glory.
We ask this in the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation.
How did it go?
I think it's a good move.
We would like to thank you for your support.
Thank you.
Four of them can put us against the personal appearances.
Five claims list.
We're going to pull out the clients for any old concrete.
No, both of them separately.
So we'll vote first on the ones.
All other besides in your concrete.
Most two approve.
I'll second.
Okay.
Parker.
Hi.
Hitman.
Jones.
Hi.
Now the claim is involving in your concrete.
In deserving as we be forward, we'll have to do several things.
That's because Dustin works in your concrete.
So the managers at so we'll have a separate panel.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Marker.
Hitman.
Sorry.
Jones.
Hi.
All right.
Step.
Six.
Annual well state bank contract process.
Utility payments for the MIMA special utility of the city.
So this is actually six and seven kind of together.
The first ones for a real estate bank.
And the second one is for a personal bank item number seven.
These are the same two banks that we have contracts with this last year.
We were kind of on a short timeline to get these contracts in front of you because of the change
over we had customer service so we aren't going to go out and reach out to the other.
banks, you know, to give them the opportunity. But these are the two that we have in place.
Currently, it's working really well. They do a great job for us.
We'll make a motion where we'll prove line out in six and seven.
Let's try again.
Parker.
Hi.
Jones.
Thank you.
Hey, Gidel Stratton, Edmunds and Palmer Claim.
We're realizing seeing in the amount of 1,260 dollars.
This is for professional services.
In this verse, I'm going to take care of from March 18 to April 19, 2024.
This is for being the MCG issues.
We're realizing the exciting plan.
The end of the minute.
The survey court of appeals follows.
So balance is $320,947.
If this invoice is approved for $1,260.
That'll leave us a balance of $319,680.
And $470.
Make a motion away.
Then call.
Hi.
No.
Later, engagement will the end for rate study update.
Put the GRDA electric rate increase.
And review water and sewer rates.
Good evening.
MSUA board.
This is for will day entry.
VR rates.
As we said, GRDA is raising up to the amount of electric rates.
4% for the next three years.
And I also, everybody should have in front of them and pack it.
That is showing just some different things.
So I know to be clear.
I know that people will say it's because of the lawsuit.
We're going to end.
There's lots of people there.
So I know to be clear.
I know that people will say it's because of the lawsuit.
We're going to end.
So there's lots of people there.
So if you see if your company just keeps us in front of each other's class, so we are in the wholesale transmission.
So, you know, we, the transmission lines feed our substations, and so that's how we get our power.
So there's other cities that are also in that that will get the 4% increase, not just the city of Miami.
In the RDA's, I mean, obviously municipalities and also, you know, private business and industrial parts.
So, in the packet, I also included their rating increases that they're talking about a house broke down by the different rate classes.
And as a household, it's just in the process of updating their shutdown because it's increasing.
Another's information on us being currently in contract with GRDA, is there an extended amount of time that we're in contract with him?
20.
Yes.
We know it.
How much profit?
300.
3.
So the profits of this rates study would be to find out if we sit into this bracket?
No, the first of our rates, isn't, if we get just our rates to get it, what safety and comfort percentage increase.
Because what we're going to have to raise our rates for us, we're going to have to subsidize and somehow, you know, the increasing.
And also, if other doing something, we need you to get our Warrens, through rates like that.
Yeah.
We need to see what we need to be doing.
We'll sit in our capital and criminal list, but we're going to do the making increase year days, doing.
We'll still have to add to that.
So they can update to our rates should be.
When does the first
Jardier, a poor percentage increase to October 1st of 2024, will be october 1st of the fall years less and I mean, you know, obviously
I've never gotten ever released it with being the fall
I know they can't just say they want to do it in the summer when I please don't because you know that's the stuff people have you know that he does the new year
When is the the year
So the action item here is we're voting to have will band you as bridge steady?
Yes sir.
That's the cost of the 26,000.
So all that steady take.
And that depends on how fast we can get all the time.
So we want to see you.
You know, it's not considered right.
The majority of people are different rates.
We're going to be a professor.
So if I was an outsider looking in, I would be thinking we're going to spend money
because we're going to have to spend more money to spend more money.
So that we can charge more money when our citizens are getting charge more money from not just us
with GRDA.
That makes sense.
That little bit of it.
I mean, from the standard citizen, that's the perspective it is.
So we're going to raise, we're going to our GRDA rates raised.
So you guys want to see if you want to raise our other rates as well.
And we're going to pay to get that study done to see if we need to raise those rates.
And that's what it looks like if you just write it out and black and white.
And I know it's the right thing to do.
Yeah.
I thought that as we have to.
It's a very strong that we have to raise rates because the GRDA is raising right now.
So let me ask you this.
If we just raise rates and didn't do the study and saved the money, could we raise rates less?
I mean, there was two of us that calculated that when our storm here would build,
myself and another gentleman.
And I mean, it was bought on nobody's ever done that before.
And be honest with you.
but it would be a number of other items.
You don't do this for a living.
I think it's a most fair that people I know
is $26,000, but I think it's
the most fair way to know exactly what it is.
Well, it's a most ethical.
Keep say a fix, a line within the outside.
It's kind of the reason they use them.
It's got sea charge.
And then if they're changing their capacity charge,
they're recharged, they're off being on peak.
Until we don't, we don't charge off peak and on peak rates
because we have no way to mark this.
So you need to have to calculate that.
And I calculate that you're going to do because
they're a customer, they use a lot of energy then.
And there is a discussion on that.
Guess the other question is, is this something
that we've already budgeted?
Yes, it would take that commercial services.
Well, I'll make a motion to approve.
Yes, that's correct.
10.
A board of audit services to HBCCPAs and advisors for RFP24-32,
authorized to submit their sign letter, engagement, contingent,
and bond legal approval.
Mayor and Council periodically.
We need to change our auditing service.
service to get new insight, perspective, and our financial statements.
We saw proposals for year ending June 30, 2024.
We sent out requests for proposals to 15 different accounting firms and receive proposals
from Hinkle and Company, HBC, CPAs and advisors.
And we had one came in late from thinly and cook that we weren't able to put into the process.
Our evaluation checklist showed that HBC scored 101 points and that Hinkle and Company scored 98 points.
HBC and advisors also offered the lowest bid and they came in at 3,100 less than Hinkle and Company.
We recommend setting up a contract with HBC and advisors and to do our annual financial audit this coming this next audit and we need your approval.
How long will that contract be for? Is it one year or is it?
We'll be setting it up for a year at a time.
Is this another new that we've never used before?
We haven't used them now.
Could we use them before?
But I didn't bid at all.
I said one year, I need to look at that.
It could be three, I think it's one.
And we're in the position right now that we can go whatever direction.
You know, we're still doing the right thing.
We're still doing the right thing that we're going to do.
Maybe we can ask for three in the price of the change.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm New Business.
I'm meeting with the residents of the post in this agenda.
12 staff reports.
13.
Trustee community announcements.
14.
This meeting will be continued from council chamber to remain in the staff room for the purpose
of executive session at the agenda item's effort to agenda item 17 of the regular meeting
of the council.
Uh-huh.